Unicorns secret.
Billions burned before they vanish, often goes unnoticed,
despite the massive capital injections
that fuel their rapid ascent.
These high growth startups prioritize market share
and user acquisition over immediate profitability,
a strategy known as blitz scaling,
driving an insatiable demand for venture capital.
This relentless pursuit of scale demands astronomical burn rates
with companies frequently spending hundreds of millions
annually on expansion, marketing, and talent,
often without a clear path to sustainable revenue.
When funding cycles tighten or market sentiment shifts,
these once hyped giants, lacking fundamental profitability,
abruptly collapse, leaving behind a trail of vanished capital
and unfulfilled promises.
A cycle some argue is an unavoidable cost of innovation,
which makes you wonder why unicorns secret billions
burned before they vanish often goes unnoticed.